I wanted to have uniforms made.
The logo should be square like this.
We like the colors of the members.
I mean, overall.
All the colors.
Maybe a white background with a line or a belt in the member's color.
You can have skirts or short pants.
Or half pants or long pants.
The image of the belt?
Except for the belt at 5
I am in art
I like
I like skirts like this.
Cheerleader style?
Cheerleader kind.
The top is a little big, and you can put it in and make it look good.
With the Chi logo on the belt.
And the back?
On the back, I wanted a microphone number.
Minus?
Mike number.
Uniform number?
Nine.
Number 9?
I feel like it's the same font as before.
I don't want the name.
I don't need a name.
Would you prefer to have it?
It'll be on the uniform, right?
Well, you know, for the price.
Is it more print?
Or the length of the name could vary from person to person.
That's the thing.
It's a pain in the ass to have to make T-shirts.
I'm just thinking, it would be nice if there was some kind of uniformity.
from a sports fan's point of view.
It's in there, right?
I'd be happier if it's in there. I'd be more than happy to have it in there.
I want Otani's shirt.
Otani?
Yes, that's right.
Not a shirt with his number on it.
It's like, “This person had this number at that time.
Sometimes it changes.
That's true.
I'm pretty happy about that, from a sports oversports point of view.
Oh, if you put it in the slack...
Oh, well, sure.
Because they'll all be about the same size.
Sure, if it's like two or three letters.
Then I'll put your name in there too.
Non, cannon.
Non.
Theo.
Theo, your English is a little lame.
That one, right?
You know...
It's like high socks.
High socks?
Or loose socks.
I like loose socks, or non, you know...
these...
OK.
Thank you very much.
Yes, ma'am.
Please do.
Non.
Theo, there was a little bit of English in there.
Cute.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
The bottom is the belt and the top is the lettering on the clothes
With this belt.
Above is this lettering.
Yes, ma'am. Yes, sir.
Yes, sir. - Yes, sir.
Yes. - Yes.
Here.
Yes, sir.
What does it say?
It's a little...
Snaker.
Superstar.
Well, well, well.
That's what they say over there.
I'll do my best.
Yay.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
I'm...
Amazing.
You're so cute.
Wait a minute.
It's short.
This is the most money I've ever made.
Get in here.
That's great.
Cute.
There are so many pelts.
It's cute.
It's the most expensive.
For sure.
I do that too.
And they do that too.
This is amazing.
It's cute.
It's amazing. It's so cute.
It's amazing.
The way it walks.
Dirt.
Deden. Deden.
Deden.
About as much of a summer asshole as you can get.
Yeah.
Atmosphere,
Nice.
The expensive one.
The most expensive one.
Shoes are the most expensive, too.
You're going to do it?
These are cute.
But I..,
I think I can win pretty well.
Yes, I think so.
I think I can win the project.
Okay, I'll go.
Ray.
Left, too.
Oh, great.
One more thing.
One more.
Okay, okay.
OK, OK.
OK.
Oh, I feel good.
I want to jump too.
Do me too.
OK.
Ready.
Okay, okay.
OK.
OK. OK, OK, OK.
OK, OK.
Lay, shout!
Kaев,
Loud.
Si disguise.
SKY, aimed at the target.
Diver character time.
Well done!
Many things were chosen.
Yes, Narito,.
I thought up the one I think is the cutest.
So I thought mine was the cutest.
I knew I had to have this embroidery.
You went to a lot of trouble to make the embroidery one.
And this one, too.
I asked him to put my name and microphone number inside.
I'm really happy to have this one made fluffy
It's so cute!
And I also had a belt made.
This was made with a 3D printer.
I even requested shoes.
I told him I wanted these superstars.
The most expensive one, and the most expensive outfit I've put on that suit.
I'm so happy!
I'm so glad that you could make it exactly as I wanted it to be.
If this is chosen this time...
I wanted to make it in the members' colors.
I wanted to make it in each member's color.
I wanted to make it in different colors.
And then, in the middle of the show
Shuffle
Shuffle all the parts and stuff.
We all swapped outfits.
So
I mean, you get to wear the costumes of the other girls.
You can see the other girls in their costumes.
For example, I'm wearing green, or pink, etc. For example, I might wear green or pink.
I might wear green or pink.
I might wear green or pink, and other girls might wear this outfit.
I think it's going to be a fun FC tour for sure.
I'm sure it will be a fun FC tour and I'll be happy to see you in these cute costumes.
I would be happy if I could see you in these cute outfits.
Please vote for us!